So I've said this elsewhere in the course, but I want to make it clear, for those of you who are really
interested in finance, beware of marketers in order to help you be more cognizant of those who might
be trying to trick you.
I'm going to make you an offer.
Anyone, even students who are not taking this course can message me at any time and ask me, am I taking
a finance course taught by a marketer?
Of course, I can only speak to the courses where I've seen the content myself, but the few that I
have seen are ridiculously bad.
Bad enough that it prompted me to make this lecture to warn you.
Now, I won't tell you which course it is or which instructor it is, but I will give you a yes or no
answer telling you whether or not you are taking such a course.
Typically, these courses claim to teach you things like predicting stock prices with storms and they
will show you results like this with nearly perfect stock price predictions.
Of course, those who are competent in finance know that this is nonsense.
I'll also include details about what mistakes to look for in these courses so you can verify for yourself
why what they are teaching is dubious.
I've heard that they are still making these mistakes and other possibly worse mistakes to this day.
In other words, thousands and thousands of students have been learning wrong and incorrect material
for years.
Believe me, if you ever try to use something like this as part of your portfolio, when you're trying
to get a job, nobody will take you seriously.
So that's my offer to you.
If you would like to know whether or not one of the courses you are taking is taught by a known a fake
data scientist, just send me a message.
You can do that either on this platform or you can go to my Web site at lezzy program or me either way
is fine.
Thanks for listening and I'll see you in the next lecture.